== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hello.
(Leonard:)How was your day?
(Penny:)Oh, not good.
(Penny:)Still couldn't get in
to see Dr. Gallo.
(Sheldon:)A doctor?
(Sheldon:)Well, I hope
you're not contagious.
(Sheldon:)I've got a weekend
in the telescope room
(Sheldon:)I've been excited about
for almost three minutes.
(Penny:)I'm not sick.
It's for work.
(Penny:)There's this doctor who refuses
to see any sales reps.
(Penny:)I've been trying
to get in for months.
(Leonard:)Well, did you try
wearing the shirt
(Leonard:)I said was
inappropriate for work?
(Penny:)Well, the doctor's a woman,
but...
(Penny:)yes, because
you never know.
(Howard:)What kind of doctor
is she?
(Penny:)Um, a psychiatrist. Why?
(Howard:)Well, what if you make
an appointment as a patient?
(Howard:)Then you'll get to talk to her.
(Penny:)Yeah, they already know
I'm a pharmaceutical sales rep.
(Raj:)Oh. What if Leonard
made an appointment
(Raj:)and tried to lay some
groundwork for you?
(Penny:)That's interesting.
(Leonard:)I'm not gonna make
a fake appointment
(Leonard:)with a psychiatrist.
(Leonard:)What would I say
is wrong with me?
(Raj:)Low self-esteem.
Social anxiety.
(Sheldon:)Sexual insecurity.
(Leonard:)None of that is true.